<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data Analyst Portfolio on Gustavo Mello</title>
    <link>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data Analyst Portfolio on Gustavo Mello</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sales Dashboard Overview: Power Bi Visualization</title>
      <link>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>In this dashboard I built you will be able to:&#xA;Analyse the total revenue per month in a area chart where I included a tooltip to show the total profit and cost in percentage in a columm chart, total revenue and the product most saled. Analyse the most sold products in a stacked bar chart to show thr ranking. Analyse the 5 biggest clients the bought the products in a treemap chart.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales Dashboard: Profit, costs, Revenues.</title>
      <link>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2024 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>You will be able to see:&#xA;A sales report with a columm chart to visualize the total revenues per month, and boxes showing the total revenue and the quantity saled. A cost report with the costs per month in a columm chart, and fixed boxes with total costs, total inventory cost, total production cost, total transport cost. A profit report with the profit per month in a columm chart, and fixed boxes showing total revenue, total costs, total profit and profit margin.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/about/</guid>
      <description>I studied and graduated at CEFET/RJ where I graduated in administration. It was the period where I found out that I had an analytical profile, using data to solve problems, bringing the best solutions automating processes and manual tasks with VBA and Excel, for instance.&#xA;I currently work in an oil and gas company, called Subsea7, that is a global leader in the delivery of offshore projects and services for the evolving energy industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://GustavoAmorimMello.github.io/GustavoMello_Portfolio/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.&#xA;Platform URL LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/gustavoamello/ GitHub: https://github.com/GustavoAmorimMello </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
